(upbeat music)
♪ There's a boy I know ♪
♪ He's the one I dream of ♪
♪ Looks into my eyes ♪
♪ Takes me to the clouds above, mm-hmm ♪
♪ Oh, I lose control ♪
♪ Can't seem to get enough, uh-huh ♪
♪ When I wake from dreaming ♪
♪ Tell me, is it really love ♪
♪ Ooh, how will I know ♪
♪ Don't trust your feelings ♪
♪ How will I know ♪
♪ Love can be deceiving ♪
♪ How will I know if he really loves me ♪
♪ I say a prayer with every heartbeat ♪
♪ I fall in love whenever we meet ♪
♪ I'm asking you what you
know about these things ♪
♪ How will I know if he's thinking of me ♪
♪ I try to phone but I'm
too shy can't speak ♪
♪ Falling in love is so bittersweet ♪
♪ This love is strong,
why do I feel weak ♪
♪ Oh, wake me, I'm shaking ♪
♪ I wish I had you near me now, uh-huh ♪
♪ Said there's no mistaking ♪
♪ What I feel is really love ♪
♪ Ooh, tell me, how will I know ♪
♪ Don't trust your feelings ♪
♪ How will I know ♪
♪ Love can be deceiving ♪
♪ How will I know if he really loves me ♪
♪ I say a prayer with every heartbeat ♪
♪ I fall in love whenever we meet ♪
♪ I'm asking you what you
know about these things ♪
♪ How will I know if he's thinking of me ♪
♪ I try to phone but I'm
too shy, can't speak ♪
♪ Falling in love is so bittersweet ♪
♪ This love is strong,
why do I feel weak ♪
♪ If he loves me ♪
♪ If he loves me not ♪
♪ Mm, if he loves me ♪
♪ Ooh, if he loves me not ♪
♪ Hey, if he loves me ♪
♪ If he loves me not ♪
♪ Oh, how will I know ♪
♪ How will I know ♪
♪ Hey, how will I know ♪
♪ Ooh, how will I know
if he really loves me ♪
♪ I say a prayer with every heartbeat ♪
♪ I fall in love whenever we meet ♪
♪ I'm asking you 'cause you
know about these things ♪
♪ How will I know if he's thinking of me ♪
♪ I try to phone but I'm
too shy, can't speak ♪
♪ Falling in love is so bittersweet ♪
♪ This love is strong,
why do I feel weak ♪
♪ How will I know ♪
♪ I say a prayer ♪
♪ Ooh, how will I know ♪
♪ I fall in love ♪
♪ How will in know, hey, how will I know ♪